careers.vic.gov.au 2015-06-10

# Privacy Policy - Careers

> <p>Government's Privacy Statement </p>

The careers.vic.gov.au website (careers website) and the Victorian Government careers mobile app provide access to the Victorian Government's online recruitment service. It streamlines the recruitment process, making it easier for you to apply for a job with the Victorian Government.

**What you should know**

The eRecruitment process is designed to protect the privacy of you personal information. This Privacy Collection Notice provides you with an account of the ways in which your personal information is collected and handled within the eRecruitment system. This includes any personal information you provide when: 

  * Registering for an account with the careers website 

  * Creating a candidate profile 

  * Submitting a job application 

  * Registering to receive job email alerts 

Providing you with notice about the collection and handling of your personal information is a requirement under the Victorian _Information Privacy Act 2000._

Your personal information is collected for recruitment and workforce planning purposes within the Victorian Government. Recruitment purposes include considering and responding to your job applications, providing you with information about prospective jobs or enabling you to receive relevant job alerts. 

Recruitment information may also be used for workforce planning purposes. This involves HRX and the Victorian Government departments/agencies generating activity analysis reports and performance analytics. These reports do not contain any identifying personal information. Otherwise, your personal information may only be used and disclosed as permitted under the _Information Privacy Act 2000._

**Is online recruitment secure?**

From the moment your information is submitted to the careers website it is subject to a range of rigorous secruity protections including encryption, firewalls and auditing and monitoring of access to the eRecruitment system. 

**Access to your own information**

You may access your own information and update your details via your eRecruitment account at any time. Once you have submitted a job application it is not possible to amend the application itself. If you would like to edit an application please contact the relevant hiring department to change details within your application. 

For enquiries relating to privacy issues at careers.vic.gov.au please contact 

Privacy Officer 

Victorian Public Sector Commission  
3 Treasury Place  
Melbourne 3000 VIC  
Email: [privacy@vpsc.vic.gov.au](mailto:privacy@ssa.vic.gov.au)  
Telephone: 03 9651- 5309 

  * **Home**
    1. [Graduate Opportunities](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/graduate-opportunities)
    2. [Job Search](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/job-search)
    3. [Career Services](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/career-services)
    4. [Register](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/register)
    5. [Application Process](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/application-process)
    6. [Tips for Applying](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/tips-for-applying)
    7. [Key Selection Criteria](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/key-selection-criteria)
    8. [Working in Government](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/working-in-government)
    9. [Profiles](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/profiles)
    10. [A Fair Workplace](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/a-fair-workplace)
    11. [Career Structure](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/career-structure)
    12. [Career Planning](http://careers.vic.gov.au/vacancies/related-sites)
    1. [People with a Disability](http://careers.vic.gov.au/why/people-with-a-disability)
    2. [Benefits and Conditions](http://careers.vic.gov.au/why/benefits-conditions)
    3. [Our Culture](http://careers.vic.gov.au/why/our-culture)
    4. [Make a Difference](http://careers.vic.gov.au/why/make-a-difference)
    5. [Testimonials](http://careers.vic.gov.au/why/testimonials)
    1. [Job Outlook](http://careers.vic.gov.au/about/job-outlook)
    2. [Living in Victoria](http://careers.vic.gov.au/about/living-in-victoria)
    3. [Government in Victoria](http://careers.vic.gov.au/about/government-in-victoria)
    4. [Locations](http://careers.vic.gov.au/about/locations)
    1. [Opportunities For Aboriginal Applicants](http://careers.vic.gov.au/exploration/opportunties-for)
    2. [Karreeta Yirramboi](http://careers.vic.gov.au/exploration/karreeta-yirramboi)
    3. [Profiles](http://careers.vic.gov.au/exploration/karreeta-yirramboi-profiles)
    4. [Pick Vic - resource for students and career coordinators ](http://careers.vic.gov.au/exploration/student-and-career-coordinator-resources)
    5. [Senior Appointments](http://careers.vic.gov.au/exploration/senior-appointments)
    6. [A Career Plan](http://careers.vic.gov.au/exploration/a-fair-workplace)
    7. [Career Toolkit](http://careers.vic.gov.au/exploration/career-structure)
    8. [Career Tips & Ideas](http://careers.vic.gov.au/exploration/theworld)
    9. [Job Programs](http://careers.vic.gov.au/exploration/job-programs)
    1. [Frequently Asked Questions](http://careers.vic.gov.au/contactus/faqs)
    2. [Department / Agency Contacts ](http://careers.vic.gov.au/contactus/department-agency-contacts)
  * **Career Miscellaneous**
    1. Site Map
    2. Printer Help
    3. FAQ's
    4. Copyright
    5. Related Links
    6. Accessibility
    7. Disclaimer
    8. Privacy Policy
  * **Contact Us**
